From a young age, many of us learn the benefits of being an extrovert – those gregarious individuals who always seem to be the life and soul of the party, often outspoken and able to express their opinions easily.
从很小的时候起，我们很多人就被灌输外向者的种种好处——那些爱交际的人似乎永远是派对的灵魂人物，他们往往直言率真，能轻松表达自己的观点。
However, not all of us are wired that way – so is being an extrovert really better?
但并非所有人天生如此——那么，做外向者真的更好吗？
While thinking of extroverts, we imagine a character who is assertive, approachable, cheerful and charming.
一想到外向者，我们脑海中浮现的形象往往是自信果敢、平易近人、开朗迷人的。
We are taught to admire these traits early on.
我们从小就被教导要欣赏这些特质。
Kids are often encouraged to interact, play and communicate with other children.
大人们总是鼓励孩子去和同龄人互动、玩耍、交流。
It seems at times as though children are made to embrace a more outgoing lifestyle, with some people becoming pseudo-extroverts – introverts who mimic extrovert behaviour.
有时，孩子们仿佛被迫去接纳更外向的生活方式，甚至有些人会变成“伪外向者”——也就是模仿外向者行为的内向者。
While externally they seem to enjoy the company of others, or being in the limelight, they can still become over-extended in intense social situations.
虽然从表面上看，他们似乎享受他人的陪伴，或是乐于成为众人关注的焦点，但在高强度的社交场合中，他们依然会感到心力交瘁。
So, while the positive aspects of being an extrovert are plain to see, what are the benefits of introversion?
所以，尽管外向者的优点显而易见，但内向又有哪些好处呢？
While extroverts thrive on social interaction, introverts are more comfortable with levels of isolation.
外向者在社交互动中汲取能量，而内向者则更能适应独处的状态。
According to Dr Berit Brogaard, a professor of philosophy, extreme solitude, such as times like the recent lockdown, does not affect introverts as much as extroverts.
哲学教授贝丽特·布罗加德博士表示，像此前封锁那样的极端独处环境，对内向者的影响远小于外向者。
Lack of social contact, something extroverts thrive on, can lead to depression, loneliness, and even premature death.
外向者赖以生存的社交互动的缺失，可能会导致抑郁、孤独，甚至过早离世。
But it’s not just in an extreme situation that the pros of being an introvert shine through.
但内向者的优势并非只在极端情况下才显现。
These people seem to have more time for contemplation and introspection and thus can become more balanced.
这类人往往有更多时间进行思考和内省，因此能拥有更平和的心态。
They also tend to be good listeners and think before they speak, meaning they could become great friends.
他们还通常是很好的倾听者，说话前会经过深思熟虑，这意味着他们能成为很棒的朋友。
Finally, introverts are often fantastic observers, as sitting out of the focus can give you more time to watch the behaviour of others.
最后，内向者往往是出色的观察者，因为远离焦点能让他们有更多时间去留意他人的言行举止。
So, whatever your personality, either introvert or extrovert, there are clear advantages to being either, and if you meet an introvert, you might just end up with an amazing friend.
因此，无论你是哪种性格，内向也好，外向也罢，二者都有各自鲜明的优点。如果你认识一位内向者，说不定最终会收获一段珍贵的友谊。